다이간다는 방을 밝게 하고 적당히 떨어져서 봐!
Watch Daigunder in a bright room and keep some distance!
Смотри Дайгандера со включённым светом, сидя подальше от экрана!
다이간다!
Daigunder!
Дайгандер!
다다다다다다다다다!
Dadadada da da da dada
Дададада-да-да-да-дада!
다다다다다다다다다!
Dadadada da da da dada
Дададада-да-да-да-дада!
다이 다이 다이 다이 다이간다
Dai Dai Dai Dai Daigunder
Дай-Дай-Дай-Дай-Дайгандер
불타라 불타올라라
Burn and flare up
Пыл борьбы разожги ты в себе,
마음의 눈을 열어라
Open your eyes of soul
Распахни шире око души
폭투선언 다이간다
Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder!
(Bakutou Sengen Daigunder)
Боевой претендент Дайгандер!
뜨거운 마음을 담아
With all your hot heart
Пусть меня охватит твой жар сердца,
오늘도 기적을 맹새해
I will make a miracle today too
Чтобы сотворить сумел я чудо
드래곤 소드 작렬이야
Dragon Sword bursts
Вспыхнет ярким светом Меч Дракона!
싸워야 할 라이벌은
The rival I have to fight against is
Побороть я должен свой упавший дух,
좌절하려는 내 자신
right here, dispirited myself
что пути к успеху преграждает мне,
어제보다도 진화해서
Evolve even more than yesterday
Вырасти сегодня больше, чем вчера
강해져라!
And become strong!
И сильнее стать!
다다다다 다 다 다 다다
Dadadada da da da dada
Дададада-да-да-да-дада!
드래곤 캐논!
Dragon Cannon!
Пушка Дракона!
다이 다이 다이 다이 다이간다
Dai Dai Dai Dai Daigunder
Дай-Дай-Дай-Дай-Дайгандер
불타라 불타올라라
Burn and flare up
Пыл борьбы разожги ты в себе
에너지 전개로
Open up all your energy and
Дай энергии выход, сказав...
다다다다다다 다
Dadadadadada da
Дададададада-да!!
다이 다이 다이 다이 다이간다
Dai Dai Dai Dai Daigunder
Дай-Дай-Дай-Дай-Дайгандер
쓰러트려라 타도해라
Defeat and knock down
Победи и врагов одолей
빛나는 강철의
Fighter of shining steel
Сталью сверкает тело твоё,
폭투선언 다이간다
Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder
Боевой претендент Дайгандер
제 26 화
The 26th Episode
Эпизод 26
진상선언!
Truth Declaration!
대우주의 대결투!!
A Great Dual in the Great Space!!
(en: Daigunder My Thumb)
제 1, 제 2 엔진 체크.
The first and second engines are ready.
제 3, 제 4 엔진 체크.
The third and fourth engines are ready.
전 엔진 체크 완료! 발사 준비 완료!
All engines check complete! Ready to depart!
목적지는 우주 공간! 드라고버스트의 본거지다!
We're going to the Space, where Dragoburst is!
스페이스 다이셔틀 출발!
Space Daishuttle, take off!
긴잔, 아, 용서할 수 없소!
Ginzan, ah, you're unforgivable!
네가 배신만 안 했으면 드라고버스트가 어디 있는 지는 진즉에 알았소!
If you didn't betray us, we would be knowing where Dragoburst is by now-gozaru!
배신이라? 뭔 소리냐.
Betray? I don't know what you're talking about.
적반하장이라는 것은, 아, 네놈 말이요!
What it means by "the guilty is audacious" is you!
하지메 박사를 구하러 하다니 용서할 수 없소!
Trying to rescue Prof. Hajime is totally unforgivable-gozaru!
그래서 어쩔 거냐?
So what?
아, 당연한 걸!
ah, how obvious is that!
소인들의 손으로 자네를 ○○ 시켜 주겠소!
We'll make you ○○-gozaru!
재밌군.
Interesting.
그만둬라.
Stop that.
너희들이 싸워봤짜 해결은 되지 않는다.
No conclusion is to be made by fighting for you guys.
그렇지만, 아, 이 놈은!
But, ah, this guy is...!
-어라라.
-어, 어디 가시오?!
-Whaaaat?
-W- where are you going to-gozaru?!
여긴 잡음이 너무 많다.
There are too much noise here.
드라고버스트를 잡으라니. 하지메 박사를 유괴하라니. 이제 됐다!
Catch Dragoburst? Kidnap Prof. Hajime? I've heard enough!
난 내 길을 걷는다. 그리고 다이간다를 쓰러뜨린다.
I will take my own path. And take down Daigunder.
긴잔!
Ginzan!
기다리시오!
Stop-gozaru!
냅두어라.
Let him be.
드라고버스트는 다이간다를 노리고 있다. 그리고 이 내가 놈을 손에 넣으면...
Dragoburst is looking for Daigunder. And if I take him into my hands...
드라고버스트의 힘으로, 아, 다이간다로 우리의 것!
By the power of Dragoburst, ah, Daigunder is also ours!
그러면 긴잔도 돌아올 것이오!
If we do so, then Ginzan will come back-gozaru!
아, 다이셔틀!
ah, Daishuttle!
무슨!
Unbelievable!
우주 공간은 드라고버스트의 세력권 안이다. 방심하면 안 된다.
The Space is under the influence of Dragoburst. Do not let your guards down.
-알았어, 형님!
-알았어모그!
-Roger, bro!
-Got it-mogu!
데스펙터! 트라이혼! 마음 단단히 먹어라!
Despector! Trihorn! Be prepared for anything!
OK, 보스!
OK, boss!
알겠군. 드라고버스트의 본거지는 우주다.
I get it. Dragoburst is in the Space.
기동대도적인 우리가, 아, 우주대도적이 될 날이 왔소!
Today is the day for us to, ah, change from Great Mobile Thief to Great Space Thief!
대우주를 제패하고 훌륭하게 드라고버스트를 손에 넣는 것이오!
We'll rule over the Space and take Dragoburst into our hands-gozaru!
아5, 아4, 아3, 아2, 아1!
ah5, ah4, ah3, ah2, ah1!
점화이오!
Ignition-gozaru!
아, 발사!
ah, take off!
자, 가오! 무한의 우주에!
Let us go to the infinite Space!
-대우주는
-멀었소!
-The great Space is
-far far away-gozaru!
드라고플레임하고 드라고프리저. 그리고 드라고버스트.
Dragoflame, Dragofreezer, and Dragoburst.
나하고 다이쿤 교수, 아니, 프로페서 빅뱅이 공동으로 설계하고 완성한 배틀 로봇이다.
Prof. Daikun, no, Professor Big Bang and I have cooperated in planning and developing.
그렇지만 그는 탄생 이후 곧 모습을 숨겼다.
But as soon as he was born, he hid himself.
그리고 결국 돌아왔다.
And finally, he showed himself again.
다이간다를 파트너로 만들겠다는 야망을 갖고.
With the ambition of making Daigunder into his partner.
나는 아키라의 파트너. 팀 아키라의 일원이야. 만약 산산조각이 되더라고 하더라도 놈의 유혹엔 안 넘어가!
I am your partner, Akira, and a member of Team Akira. Even if I end up being teared apart, I won't accept him!
나라고 해도, 뭔 일이 있어도 너희들을 드라고버스트에게는 안 넘겨줄 거야!
Me too! No matter what, I'm not passing you guys to Dragoburst!
그래! 다이간다는 우리가 지킨다!
Right! We'll protect Daigunder!
드라고버스트 따위는 지옥에 보내 주겠어!
We'll send Dragoburst to hell!
우리에게 다 맡겨모그!
Leave everything to us-mogu!
섣부른 소리 마라. 우리는 싸우러 온 게 아니다.
Don't be so hot-tempered. We're not here to fight.
고도의 지능과 의지를 가진 드라고버스트를 설득한다.
We'll persuade Dragoburst with high intellectual quality and will.
그들의 능력은 우리 사회에 큰 도움이 될 터. 그걸 위해서도 차분히 이야기할 필요가 있다.
Their abilities will be helpful to our society. For that too, we will have to talk with them carefully.
경계 경보야.
It's an warning alarm.
두 대의 비행 물체가 접근 중이야.
Two flying objects are approaching.
-드라고플레임!
-드라고프리저!
-Dragoflame!
-Dragofreezer!
-저 자식들! 선제 공격이냐!
-가자! 트라이혼!
-Those bastards! Attacking in advance?!
-Let's go, Trihorn!
복수하겠어모그!
We'll pay back-mogu!
-잠깐!
-다들 일단 내려놔라!
-Wait!
-Calm down, you guys!
환영한다, 제군.
Welcome, gentlemen.
-이 목소리는
-드라고버스트.
-This voice must be
-Dragoburst's.
환영할 준비는 되어 있다. 드라고플레임과 드라고프리저를 따라와라.
I am ready to greet you. Follow Dragoflame and Dragofreezer.
뭐야, 저거.
What's that?
저기다. 내 계산에 따르면 드라고버스트는 저기에 있다.
That's the place. According to my calculations, Dragoburst is in there.
여기가 드라고버스트의 비밀 기지.
So this place is Dragoburst's hideout.
폐기된 우주 스테이션과 인공 위성을 이용해서 만든 것 같구나.
It seems that he used abandoned Space Station and satellites to make this.
자, 슬슬 답을 얻을 때야!
Now, it's time for answers!
다들 가자!
Let's go, everyone!
그래!
Right!
어디야, 여긴?
What is this place?
어두워서 잘 안 보여.
It's too dark to see anything.
계산대로 됐군. 1분 1초도 안 틀리고.
It's just as my calculation, without an error even up to a minute or a second.
드라고버스트!
Dragoburst!
어디 있냐! 모습을 드러내!
Where are you?! Show yourself!
드라고버스트! 널 만든 하나 하지메다!
Dragoburst! I am Hajime, one of your creators!
어떠냐. 날 기억하냐?
Do you remember me?
잊을 수 없지. 하지메 박사와 다이쿤 교수. 그리고 내 탄생을 보았던 인간들을.
I do not forget you people, Prof. Hajime and Prof. Daikun, and everyone else who saw my birth.
나는 본능적으로 깨달았다. 인간은 내 우수한 능력을 자신만을 위해 쓸 거라는 것을.
I instinctively acknowledged that humans will use my superior powers only for their own goods.
그런 인간과 함께하고 싶지 않아서 넌 연구소를 파괴하고 숨은 것이구나.
You destroyed the lab and hid yourself because you did not want to join such people. Right?
그렇다.
Right.
모든 인간이 그렇게 생각하고 있지는 않다! 인간과 로봇은 서로 돕고 격려할 뿐이다!
Not all the humans think so! Humans and robots just help and encourage each other!
적어도 난 그렇게 생각한다!
That's what I honestly think!
드라고버스트! 난 너하고 친구가 되고 싶어! 팀메이트로 같이 싸우자!
Dragoburst! I want to be friends with you! Let's fight together as teammates!
팀 아키라에 들어오면 너도 우리가 생각하는 바를 알 수 있을 거야!
If you join Team Akira, you'll understand what we're thinking!
서로 도와? 격려해? 친구?
Help each other? Encourage? Friends?
잠깐. 뭐가 그렇게 이상해?
Hey. What's so weird about that?
나는 여기서 인간 사회를 관찰했다. 그리고 싫을 때까지 봐 왔다. 너희 인간의 흉함을.
I have been observing human society until I fed up with it. And you humans' unsightliness has never changed.
인간의 흉함이라니?
Unsightliness?
인간끼리 서로 으르렁대는 너희들이 어떻게 우리 배틀 로봇하고 신뢰 관계를 만들겠다는 것이냐.
How are you going to build a trust relationship with us battle robots, when you humans snarl at each other?
분명 그럴 지도 모른다. 그렇지만 인간은 반성하며 성장해 미래를 헤쳐나간다.
That might be true, but humans self-reflect and grow to through the future.
인간에게 미래는 없다.
Humans have no future.
나는 선언한다. 로봇의, 로봇에 의한, 로봇을 위한 사회를 건설하겠다고.
I hereby declare that I will build a society of the robots, by the robots, for the robots.
로봇을 위한 사회?
Soceity for the robots?
결국 미래를 제패하는 건, 그래, 우리 로봇이다.
At last, the one that rules the future is, yes, us robots.
뭐야?
What?
류구. 건더. 아니, 다이간다. 나와 함께 로봇의 유토피아를 만들지 않겠나.
Ryugu. Gunder. No, Daigunder. Wouldn't you like to make a utopia for robots with me?
뭐?!
What?!
유토피아라고?
Utopia?!
폭투선언 다이간다
Bakutou Sengen Daigunder
Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder
Боевой претендент Дайгандер
by Subdivers
Russian TL by SutoKuroi
Subdivers 번역
폭투선언 다이간다
Bakutou Sengen Daigunder
Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder
Боевой претендент Дайгандер
by Subdivers
Russian TL by SutoKuroi
Subdivers 번역
다이간다는 실로 우수한 배틀 로봇. 그래. 나와 다이간다가 손을 잡으면 무엇이라도 실현 가능하다.
Daigunder is a truly superior battle robot. When Daigunder and I work together, anything is possible.
손을 잡아?
Work together?
합체 말이다.
He's talking about fusion.
그 영상은 역시 네가...
It really was you who sent that video...
흥. 다이간다를 내 파트너로 데려가기 위한 인사다.
Hmph. This is a greeting to take Daigunder as my partner.
난 아키라하고 함께 싸워 왔어! 앞으로도 쭉 함께야. 너하고 파트너 따위는 안 해!
I kept fighting with Akira, and will keep doing so! I will never be a partner with you!
류구하고 건더는 못 건네준다!
You won't take Ryugu and Gunder from us!
네가 바라는 대로는 안 된다!
You won't get what you want!
맞아모그!
He's right-mogu!
드라고버스트, 다시 한번 생각해 봐라! 나하고 올 생각 없나!
Dragoburst, please think once again! Wouldn't you like to come with me?
거절한다. 너희들이 날 방해하도록 두지 않을 게다.
I refuse. I won't let you interfere me.
류구! 건더!
Ryugu! Gunder!
잠깐! 기다려라, 드라고버스트!
Wait! Just one more moment, Dragoburst!
안녕이다, 하지메 박사.
Farewell, Prof. Hajime.
류구!
Ryugu!
안돼! 공기가!
No! The air!
파이터 체인지!
Fighter Change!
류구! 건더! 합체해라.
Ryugu! Gunder! Combine.
다이간다가 되어라!
Become Daigunder!
파이터 체인지!
Fighter Change!
고마워, 서봇!
Thank you, Supbot!
-역시!
-덕분에 살았다!
-I knew you'd do it!
-You saved us!
어?
Huh?
류구! 건더!
Ryugu! Gunder!
안 되겠어.
I can't.
자, 해라. 헤드합체다!
Do it. Do Head Fusion!
헤드합체.
Head Fusion.
폭투왕 다이간다!
Wild Fight King Daigunder!
-무슨!
-말도 안 돼!
-No way!
-How could this be?!
좋아. 네 힘을 보여줘 봐라.
Great. Show me your powers.
드래곤 캐논.
Dragon Cannon.
아, 안 돼! 피해라!
N- no! Evade!
다이간다!
Daigunder!
전의 에너지파야. 다이간다는 드라고버스트에게 조종당하고 있어.
It's the energy wave we saw before. Daigunder is under control of Dragoburst.
나 말도 안 되는 배틀 로봇을 탄생시키고 말았구나!
I ended up making an outrageous battle robot!
인간과 로봇의 빛나는 미래를 건설하기 위해 만든 드라고버스트.
Dragoburst was made to build a bright future both for humans and robots.
그게 이런 짓을...
And he's doing this...
아키라.
Akira.
할아버지, 반성할 거면 나중에 해! 일단 다이간다를 구해야 해!
Grandpa, if you're going to reflect, then do it later! We have to rescue Daigunder first!
아키라가 말하는 대로에요.
Akira's right.
나, 갈게! 나머지는 잘 부탁해!
I'm going out! I'm leaving the rest to you!
이걸로 다이간다는 나의 것.
Daigunder has finally become mine.
내 것이다!
He's mine!
눈을 떠!
Open your eyes!
음?
Hm?
눈을 떠, 다이간다!
Wake up, Daigunder!
드라고버스트! 네 멋대로는 안 된다!
Dragoburst! We will stop you!
힘으로라도 다이간다를 돌려받겠다!
We'll take Daigunder back with force, if we have to!
웃기지 마라! 이 송사리가!
Don't make me laugh, you small fry!
-소, 송사리라고?!
-그 말, 용서할 수 없다!
-S- small fry?!
-That's unforgivable!
다이간다! 헤드합체!
Daigunder! Head Fusion!
전설의 폭투신 드래곤 다이간다!
Legendary Wild Fight God Dragon Daigunder!
드라고플레임!
Dragoflame!
드라고프리저!
Dragofreezer!
세이버 체인지!
Saber Change!
실드 체인지!
Shield Change!
내게 거역하는 것의 무의미함을 깊히 깨닫게 해 주겠다!
I will make you truly realize how futile it is to oppose me!
해 보자, 팀 아키라!
Face me, Team Akira!
다이간다! 합체 해제야!
Daigunder! Cancel Fusion!
소용 없다! 지금의 다이간다에게는 무슨 소리를 안 해도 안 통해!
It won't work! No matter what you say, Daigunder can't hear you!
썬더 클로!
Thunder Claw!
파이어 애로!
Fire Arrow!
클래시 뱅!
Clash Bang!
다이간다를 해방하기 위해서는 드라고버스트를 쓰러트릴 수밖에 없어!
The only way of freeing Daigunder is to take down Dragonburst!
티라노 슬래시!
Tyranno Slash!
스펙터 슬래시!
Spector Slash!
버스트 펄서!
Burst Pulsar!
다들!
Everyone!
단 한 방으로...
With only one hit...
포기할 수 없다!
We can't give up!
버스트 캐논!
Burst Cannon!
공격!
Attack!
뭐야?!
What?!
다들!
Everyone!
거짓된 파트너를 우리 힘으로 우주로 치우자.
Let's get rid of a false partner deep into the Space.
유토피아 건설의 첫 걸음에 어울리는 이벤트다.
It truly is an event suitable for the first step of building a utopia.
그만해, 다이간다!
Stop it, Daigunder!
소용 없다. 다이간다는 이제 내 의지로 움직이고 나와 하나다!
It's no use. Daigunder now moves by my will and is one with me!
다이간다! 다이간다!
Daigunder! Daigunder!
공격!
Attack!
파이널 리볼버!
Final Revolver!
긴잔!
Ginzan!
네이놈, 긴잔! 질리지도 않고!
Ginzan, you bastard! You should be tired by now!
네놈 따위에게 다이간다를 뺏길 수 없다!
I won't you take Daigunder away from me!
웃기지 마라! 버스트 캐논!
Don't fool around! Burst Cannon!
공격!
Attack!
파이널 리볼버!
Final Revolver!
다이간다! 아니, 류구!
Daigunder! No, Ryugu!
기억해내 줘! 모두하고 같이 한 트레이닝을!
Please remember the training you did with everyone!
나하고 같이 싸운 록코타운 토너먼트나 알바트로스 리그도!
Remember Rokkotown Tournament and Albatross League that you fought with me!
류구!
Ryugu!
돌아와 줘! 류구!
Please come back, Ryugu!
위험해! 떨어져, 아키라!
Watch out! Get away, Akira!
버스트 캐논 공격!
Burst Cannon Attack!
아키라!
Akira!
류구!
Ryugu!
아키라!
Akira!
정신 차려, 류구!
Get a grip, Ryugu!
우리 파트너잖아?
Aren't we partners?
맞아. 그리고,
Right. And also we're...
무적의
invincible
팀 아키라야!
Team Akira!
일어나라! 승리를 노려라! 뜨거워지는 고상한 열정
Stand up! Aim for the victory! The sublime passion is heating up
Встань и борись! К победе стремись! Горячая страсть нам сердца раскаляет!
뭐야, 이 빛은?
What is this light?!
클러스터 에너지!
Cluster Energy!
얼마이고 상처나도 진정한 강함을 알 때까지
No matter how it hurts, until we grasp the true strength
Пусть раны болят, не заметим того, и силы в себе, невиданные, откроем мы!
아키라의 호소에서 힘이 넘쳐나고 있어!
Akira's call is making the power overflow!
마, 말도 안 돼!
N- no way!
다이간다! 드라고버스트에서 이탈해!
Daigunder! Break away from Dragoburst!
바람을 갈라라! 가슴을 펴라! 쏜살같이
Cut the wind! Straight yourself up! At full speed
Ветер разрежь ударом! Выпрями грудь свою! Помчись вперёд
나이스 타이밍이야모그!
Good timing-mogu!
꽉 갚아 주겠어!
We'll pay this back!
숨이 멎는 배틀, 피말리는 순간이 나를 불러
Breathtaking battle! The moment on the edge is calling me
Голову битва вскружит! Держимся на краю! Азарта миг с собой вдруг позовёт
-드라고버스트!
-지옥에 보내 주겠어!
-Dragoburst!
-You're going to hell!
다들 무사했구나!
So everyone is safe!
다가가라! 간격을 좁혀라! 흥망을 결판내라
Sidle up! Lessen the distance! Settle the rise and fall
Ещё шаг вперёд! Сократи расстояние! Упав, поднимись без сомнений вновь!
당연하지.
Of course.
티라노 슬래시!
Tyranno Slash!
다이간다! 합체다!
Daigunder! Let's combine!
얼빠진 짓만 하고 있을 수는 없어 쓰려진다면 몇번이라도
No blunders anymore. No matter the number defeated,
Промашек мы больше с тобой не допустим, неважно, как много нас ждёт врагов.
일어나라! 승리를 노려라! 뜨거워지는 고상한 열정
Stand up! Aim for the victory! The sublime passion is heating up
Встань и борись! К победе стремись! Горячая страсть нам сердца раскаляет!
드래곤 리볼버!
Dragon Revolver!
얼마이고 상처나도 진정한 강함을 알고 싶어
No matter how it hurts, we want to grasp the true strength
Пусть раны болят, не заметим того, и силы найдём, невиданные
드라고플레임! 드라고프리저! 내 방패가 되어라.
Dragoflame! Dragofreezer! Become my shield.
숭고한 목적을 위해 희생해라!
Sacrifice yourselves for the sublime goal!
눈부신 반짝임 속에서 환호로 끓는 콜로세움
The Colosseum is boiling in cheer inside a dazzling glitter
Шумят голоса на трибунах арен, и в ярких огнях Колизей утопает
언젠가는 대답이 나오면 오로지 자기 자신을 믿어
When the answer comes out, we believe in nothing but ourselves
И вновь прозвучит наш главный ответ: мы верим в себя, и нет никого, кто сломит нас!
다이간다!
Daigunder!
언젠가 꼭 널 내 손에 넣어 보이겠다!
I will take you into my hands eventually!
-잠깐!
-드라고버스트!
-Wait!
-Dragoburst!
피해가 크다. 드라고버스트하고 합체했기 때문이다.
His damage is too much because he was forced to combine with Dragoburst.
우리가 입은 피해도 있다. 지금 쫒는 건 무리겠지.
We also have taken damage. It's a bad idea to chase after him now.
괜찮잖아?
Isn't it alright?
다이간다, 네가 돌아온 것으로 충분해!
Daigunder, it's everything that you came back!
고마워! 역시 넌 내 파트너야!
Thank you! You really are my partner!
그래도...
But...
이건... 드라고버스트는 이렇게 간단히는 포기 안 한다. 언젠가 다시 나타나겠지.
For this one... Dragoburst won't give up this easily. He'll appear again.
드라고버스트, 너하고 서로 깨닫게 되는 건 언제일까?
Dragoburst, when will we be able to understand each other?
나는... 나는 그 날이 올 거라고 기대하고 있어!
I'm... I'm looking for that day to come!
끝없는 꿈을 꾸고 있어
Dreaming an endless dream
Я сон бесконечный вижу опять перед собой
몇번이고 쓰러져도
I fall down over and over again
Как упал, и лечу вниз вновь и вновь.
저 구름 위에는 분명히
Up over those clouds
Там, где-то в высотах, за чертой облаков
푸른 하늘이 펼쳐져 있을 거야
a blue sky awaits
голубое небо ждёт меня!
강해지기 위해서라면 누구도 혼자서는
To be strong, nobody can ever become
Сильным быть, чтоб никто превзойти не смог
강해지고 뜨거워질 수 없어
strong and hot, by oneself
Стать сильней, горячей, сам я хочу!
불꽃의 Fight Fight Fighting soul
Flaming fightin' fightin' fighting soul
Так гори, душа, душа бойца!
용기를 마주치는 그 때
When you face your courage
Смелость повстречай, и пусть ведёт она тебя в жизни.
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
느껴져 바로 너라는 게
I can feel it, yes, it's you
Я это чувствую, да, это ты!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
다
녀
왔
어!
H
o
m
e!
Д
о
м
а!
둘은 서로의 영웅
The two are heroes of each other
Два героя - части одного, нерушимы связи,
질 수 없는 같은 내일을
They run towards to the same tomorrow
Вместе в новый день по одной тропе спешат
바라보고 달려
that they cannot lose
И не собьются с неё!
드라고버스트를 불러내기 위해 다이간다를 잡아 미끼로 쓰려는 놈들이 왔어!
They're trying to use Daigunder as a bait to call out Dragoburst!
저 놈들, 우리를 철저히 연구해서 꽤나 힘겨워!
They studied about us pretty much, and it's a difficult fight!
그래도 우리는 새로운 동료, 드라고플레임하고 드라고프리저가 있어!
But we have new friends: Dragoflame and Dragofreezer!
플레임! 프리저! 무장합체!
Flame! Freezer! Arming Fusion!
폭투선언 다이간다의 다음 이야기!
도전선언! 새로운 친구!!
Next time on Wild Fight Declaration Daigunder!
Challenge Declaration! New Friends!!